the topic of my today video is
menu live financial corporation
insurance company in canada
let's
talk about
this company
what are the requirements
and
what are the benefits of this insurance
decision made easier lives made better
at many life this is our reason for
being it is core to who we are and the
journey we are on
so our impact agenda we are staying true
to our mission in three interconnected
ways empowering health and well-being to
support the journey towards a better
life
driving inclusive economic opportunities
to create a more even playing field for
all
accelerating a sustainable future to
preserve the planet we all share
this one benefits our business our
planet and the people who call it home
united in the pursuit of our common
goals we are building a better business
to better the world
download our impact agenda
in power 16th health and wellbeing as a
health and wealth company empowering
physical and financial well-being is a
good for our business as it's for
society that's why we are making it easy
for anyone to choose healthier behaviors
and smarter financial solutions
we will continue to innovate and scale
our behavior insure and celebrate the
mental health and well-being for our
people and drive financially security
support the journey towards a better
life
in business and in life we are stronger
when we have a diversity of perspectives
to help open
up opportunities for all we are
accelerating the upward mobility of
underrepresented groups and making
financial solution more accessible by
increasing representation of women and
communities of color we can help even
the playing field and give everyone a
fair shot at success
accelerate a sustainable future as a
health and wealth company it's natural
that we are working to protect and
restore our environment
we understand that people can be healthy
if they live on an unhealthy planet
climate changing is impacting our
ability to breathe clean air excess
drinking water and safeguard against
natural disasters that's why we are
doing our part to support the transition
to our net zero economy reducing our
emissions and providing nature based
solutions to help with the planet we all
share
our impact agenda will create long-term
value for our business our communities
and the planet it's how we are building
a better business to better the world
statement of corporate privacy
principles
menu life is committed to providing our
customers with strong reliable
trustworthy and forward-thinking
solution for their most significant
financial decisions
this includes protecting the privacy of
all personal information in our care
when handling personal information we
are abide by the following corporate
primary principle information we collect
the information we collect about our
depends upon our relationship with you
which may but may include your name
contact information information about
how you use our products and services
information about your preferences
demographic and interest we only collect
information that is required for or
related to providing products and
services conducting business and better
understanding your needs
how we use personal
information
safeguards
privacy commitment
and country specific information
this is all about the manual life
investment insurance this is all about
many life and financial cooperation i
hope you like my video don't forget to
subscribe and share thank you